http://velocityad.com/privacy-policy

Our ServicesAdvertising InfoScreen NetworksContact Us
Free Planning Proposal
Privacy Policy
Velocity’s Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains how The Velocity Group, Inc. (“Velocity”, “our”, or “we”) collects, uses and discloses information gathered through the www.VelocityAd.com web site (“Web Site”) in general. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Velocity, its affiliates or any other company (unless specifically stated). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Please note: Any information collected about users of the Web Site is collected and processed by Velocity in the United States.
TABLE OF CONTENTS
Personally Identifiable Information
Sharing Personally Identifiable Information and Disclosure to Third Parties
Cookies
Your choices
Security
Consent to Transfer
Acceptance and Changes to this Privacy Policy
Personally Identifiable Information:
For general uses of the Web Site, we will collect any other information that you may send Velocity through the Web Site via a “contact us,” “help” or other similar e-mail address or form.
We will not use the information provided to these e-mail addresses for marketing purposes unrelated to your request.
Sharing Personally Identifiable Information and Disclosure to Third Parties:
Velocity may transfer, disclose and share information collected from or about Web Site Users with its related companies, licensees, and vendors for the purposes of conducting business with Web Site Users, and administering the Web Site and the creative assets contained on and transmitted through the Web Site.
Velocity does not share any personally identifiable information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marking purposes.
Unless otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy or at the time you provide your information, Velocity does not share personally identifiable information with third parties for other purposes except under the following limited circumstances:
Third parties providing services on our behalf: Velocity engages other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf and at its direction.
Examples include, without limitation, hosting and administering the Web Site, analyzing data, and providing customer and administrative service related to the Web Site.
These third parties may have access to the user information, including personally identifiable information, but only to the extent it is needed to perform their duties and functions on Velocity’s behalf.
Legal Protection: Unless otherwise prohibited by law, Velocity may process, transfer or disclose information about its users, including personally identifiable information, and may use IP addresses to identify users in cooperation with internet service providers or law enforcement agencies, to comply with a legal obligation, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Web Site and applicable laws, or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the Web Site, Authorized Users or others.
Corporate change: You consent to Velocity processing, disclosing and transferring user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation or restructuring, the sale of substantially all of its assets, or other fundamental corporate change, unless otherwise prohibited by law.
Cookies:
The Web Site does not make use of browser “cookies.”
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site either transfers to your computer’s hard drive or stores temporarily in your computer’s memory for record-keeping purposes.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies.
You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.
Web Site Usage Information and IP Addresses:
When your computer contacts our web servers (for example, when you visit the Web Site), our web servers automatically collect non-personally identifiable information (“NPII”) including Web Site usage information, which is information that describes how visitors use and navigate the Web Site, such as the date and time of access, the web page you visit immediately preceding and immediately following your visit to the Web Site, the type of web browser and computer operating system you are using, and you IP address (a number that is assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet).
We use NPII for internal purposes, such as system administration, to analyze web site usage, to make your use of the Web Site more efficient, and to audit the use of the Web Site.
Your Choices:
You may request a change to your personally identifiable information by contacting privacy@VelocityAd.com, but Velocity must approve those requests before they take full effect.
Security:
No data transmission over the internet or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
However, Velocity has taken reasonable precautions to protect the information collected through the Web Site.
Please note the Velocity cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Velocity, and you do so at your own risk.
Consent to Transfer:
In order to administer the Web Site and conduct Velocity business through the Web Site, the information you submit is collected and processed by Velocity in the United States.
By using the Web Site, registering with us, participating in any of our services or otherwise providing us with personally identifiable information, you consent to this transfer and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Velocity operates this Web Site in the United States.
If you access this Web Site from other locations, you do so on your own initiative and you are solely responsible for compliance with applicable laws.
These Terms will be construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Illinois, without regard to its conflicts of law principles, and specifically will not be governed by the United Nations Conventions on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, if otherwise applicable.
Acceptance and Changes to this Privacy Policy:
By using the Web Site, you accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.
Velocity reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, by posting such change, update or modification on the Web Site.
Subsequent access to the Web Site by Authorized Users may require your express consent to the revised Privacy Policy in force at that time.
However, Velocity will use your personally identifiable information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted your personally identifiable information, unless you give us your consent to do otherwise.
About Us
Privacy Policy
For Networks
Velocity Digital Advertising
998 Church St. #220 Glenview, IL. 60025
Wanna talk?
Call us at (614) 581-3037
Not a big talker?
Email us at info@velocityad.com
Just want numbers?
Fill out our Free Planning Proposal
©2001 - 2018 The Velocity Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
